<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <!-- Maintenance Types -->
    <string name="brake_maintenance">Maintenance of Brakes</string>
    <string name="disc_pads_maintenance">Maintenance of Disc Pads</string>
    <string name="cables_and_housing_maintenance">Maintenance of Cables and Housings</string>
    <string name="cassette_maintenance">Maintenance of Cassette</string>
    <string name="chain_maintenance">Maintenance of Chain</string>
    <string name="rear_derailleur_maintenance">Maintenance of Rear Derailleur</string>
    <string name="frame_bearings_maintenance">Maintenance of Frame Bearings</string>
    <string name="rear_hub_maintenance">Maintenance of Rear Hub</string>
    <string name="disc_brake_maintenance">Maintenance of Disc Brakes</string>
    <string name="dropper_post_maintenance">Maintenance of Dropper Post</string>
    <string name="fork_maintenance">Maintenance of Fork</string>
    <string name="front_hub_maintenance">Maintenance of Front Hub</string>
    <string name="rear_suspension_maintenance">Maintenance of Rear Suspension</string>
    <string name="thru_axle_maintenance">Maintenance of Thru Axle</string>
    <string name="tire_maintenance">Maintenance of Tires</string>
    <string name="wheelset_tubeless_maintenance">Tubeless Fluid Replacement</string>
    <string name="wheelset_wheels_and_spokes_maintenance">Wheels and Spokes Inspection</string>
    <string name="wheelset_tread_wear_maintenance">Tread Wear Inspection</string>

    <string name="brake_maintenance_description">Perform hydraulic circuit purging and piston maintenance for optimal brake performance.</string>
    <string name="disc_pads_maintenance_description">Visually inspect disc pads for wear or damage. Replace if necessary to ensure efficient braking.</string>
    <string name="cables_and_housing_maintenance_description">Visually inspect cable housings for wear or damage. Replace if necessary to maintain smooth gear shifting.</string>
    <string name="cassette_maintenance_description">Check the wear of the cassette. Consider replacing if it shows excessive wear or hinders gear shifting.</string>
    <string name="chain_maintenance_description">Replace the chain to maintain precise gear changes and prevent excessive wear on other components.</string>
    <string name="rear_derailleur_maintenance_description">Clean and lubricate the rear derailleur mechanism for smooth and reliable shifting.</string>
    <string name="frame_bearings_maintenance_description">Check the condition and lubrication of the frame bearings. Replace if necessary to maintain frame integrity and smooth operation.</string>
    <string name="rear_hub_maintenance_description">Check the condition and lubrication of the rear hub to ensure smooth rotation and reliable performance.</string>
    <string name="disc_brake_maintenance_description">Check the wear of the disc brakes. Consider replacing if they are worn or deformed to ensure safe braking.</string>
    <string name="dropper_post_maintenance_description">Check and lubricate the adjustable seatpost for smooth operation without play or lockout.</string>
    <string name="fork_maintenance_description">Check and maintain the fork according to the manufacturer\'s recommendations for optimal suspension performance.</string>
    <string name="front_hub_maintenance_description">Check the condition and lubrication of the front hub to ensure smooth rotation and reliable performance.</string>
    <string name="rear_suspension_maintenance_description">Check and maintain the rear suspension according to the manufacturer\'s recommendations for optimal performance and comfort.</string>
    <string name="thru_axle_maintenance_description">Check the condition and proper tightening of the thru axle to ensure secure wheel attachment.</string>
    <string name="tire_maintenance_description">Check the tread wear of the tires. Consider replacing if they are worn to ensure optimal traction and safety.</string>
    <string name="wheelset_tubeless_maintenance_description">Replace tubeless fluid every 1000 km for effective sealing and prevention of punctures.</string>
    <string name="wheelset_wheels_and_spokes_maintenance_description">Inspect the condition of wheels and spokes every 1000 km. Ensure they are properly tensioned and free from visible damage to maintain wheel integrity.</string>
    <string name="wheelset_tread_wear_maintenance_description">Inspect the tread wear of the tires every 4000 km. Consider replacing if they are worn to ensure optimal performance.</string>


</resources>